Jessica Lee

Indianapolis, IN 46221 ● (425) 208 -1603 ● jp.leesilva@gmail.com ● Github ● LinkedIn ● Portfolio

It has been my dream to learn how to code for years. I have been a self-study for a while, and I just recently completed a Web Development learning program at Eleven Fifty Academy. I believe coding is a passion that will never end. I am very excited to transition into a technical role and I look forward into growing and making myself better to contribute to a company.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Java • C# • Python • JavaScript

HTML • CSS • React • Typescript • Express • Postgres SQL

Photoshop

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2019 - PRESENT

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, FLORA LEGAL GROUP

- Develop web-based tools for internal use. Using React and Express.
- Managed scheduling for staff, monitoring resource allocation to provide optimal coverage and service.
- Maintained inventory in administrative building supply closet to prevent shortages of supplies.

OCTOBER 2018 - MARCH 2019

BILINGUAL CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE, PARKER ONSITE AT NINTENDO

- Answered calls and emails in both English and Spanish to provide solutions to customer needs such as troubleshooting, network support, account management, repairs, and general questions.
- Identified consumer needs and used my own judgment to solve issues while using a large company database to provide effective solutions along with following company procedures
- Translated information on company database to be able to respond and resolve problems for Spanish speaking customers

SEPTEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2018

SERVICE MANAGER, CHIPOTLE MEXICAN GRILL

- Shift leader that allocated tasks to employees on a daily basis and monitored activity and task completion
- Managed a diverse team to reach daily and long-term goals as I mentored them on techniques necessary to complete job tasks
- Completed forecasts to determine needed inventory as well as performing scheduled inventory counts and supply audits.

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2020

WEB DEVELOPMENT, ELEVEN FIFTY ACADEMY

2014 - 2015

COMPUTER SCIENCE, BELLEVUE COLLEGE

AUGUST 2012

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MARKETING, UNIVERSIDAD DEL VALLE DE MEXICO

SKILLS

- Resourcefulness
- Quick learner
- Bilingual (Spanish)
- Time management skills
- Problem solver

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- English

PROJECTS

NERDPAL QUESTION LOGGER APP

https://nerdpal-client.herokuapp.com/

Full stack application that can create questions per user account. Then display flashcards and a Quiz

• Utilized React, Postgres, Sequelize, Express, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, styled with Semantic

STUDIO GHIBLI WATCHLIST APP

https://jl-api-studioghibli.web.app/

Movie watchlist app in which you can view information on all the movies made by Studio Ghibli. You can select which movies you have already seen and which ones to watch next.

• Utilized Ghibli API, HTML 5, CSS 3, and JavaScript

DEVHINTS SITE RECREATION

https://seytani.github.io/staticLayout-EFA/

A recreation of the site https://devhints.io/

• Utilized HTML 5, CSS 3